Hello, English learners.
你好，英语学习者。
Welcome back to EnglishPod.
欢迎回到EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我叫Marco。
Katarina And my name is Katarina.
Katarina，我叫Katarina。
So Marco, you've been shopping a lot lately.
所以Marco，你最近买了不少东西。
Marco I have.
Marco 是啊。
And this dialogue or this lesson today is one of my favorite pieces of furniture, maybe
今天这节对话或课程是关于我最近买的一件最喜欢的家具，也许是
appliances that I've bought recently, and it's a TV.
电器，那就是一台电视。
Katarina All right.
Katarina 好吧。
So I'd even go for electronics with that one.
我甚至觉得那算是电子产品。
The electronics department is somewhere you like to hang out.
电子产品区是你喜欢逛的地方。
Marco Uh-huh.
Marco 嗯哼。
I mean, I think every guy loves, you know, like a big screen TV and a home theater system.
我是说，我觉得每个男人都喜欢，你知道，大屏幕电视和家庭影院系统。
So you just like go deaf after watching.
所以你就喜欢看完后耳朵聋掉。
Katarina Why is that?
Katarina 为什么这么说？
Is bigger really better when it comes to like a 70 inch TV?
对于像70英寸电视这样的东西，越大真的越好吗？
Marco Well, I don't know.
Marco 嗯，我不知道。
I think, yeah, the whole experience of just seeing this movie on this huge TV and like
我觉得，是啊，在这台大电视上看电影的整体体验，还有
having all the sound and I don't know, it's just something about that or watching a football
所有的声音，我不知道，就是有种特别的感觉，或者和哥们儿一起看足球
game with your buddies and you can actually watch.
比赛，而且能真正看清楚。
Katarina Oh, fun.
Katarina 哦，有意思。
Okay, that I can appreciate.
好吧，这个我能理解。
But we've got a couple of great words for you.
但我们为你准备了一些很棒的词。
We're going to preview in today's vocabulary preview.
我们会在今天的词汇预览中先介绍。
Vocabulary Preview.
词汇预览。
Marco Okay, so on vocabulary preview today, we're
Marco 好的，今天的词汇预览中，我们
going to be looking at two words.
要看两个词。
The first one is to appreciate.
第一个是“appreciate”。
Katarina All right.
Katarina 好的。
So this basically means to like.
所以这基本上意味着“喜欢”。
Marco Yeah, you appreciate someone.
Marco 是的，你欣赏某人。
But in this context, to enjoy or take advantage of something.
但在这个语境中，意思是享受或利用某物。
So...
所以……
Katarina Maybe you hear this with a couple, two people
Katarina 也许你听过这个用在情侣之间，两个人
who are fighting and the girl says to the guy, you don't appreciate me.
吵架时，女孩对男孩说：“你不珍惜我。”
So he doesn't really care about her in the way that she wants him to.
所以他没有以她想要的方式关心她。
Or you could say this about a TV, for example, I can't appreciate my PS3, my great, awesome
或者你可以用来说电视，比如：“我无法享受我的PS3，我那台很棒、超棒的
console, my gaming system, because my TV is not good enough.
主机、游戏系统，因为我的电视不够好。”
Marco Or big enough.
Marco 或者不够大。
Katarina Or big enough.
Katarina 或者不够大。
Or big enough.
或者不够大。
So this means that it could be a lot better if I just bought a better TV.
所以这意味着如果我买一台更好的电视，体验会好很多。
Marco Right.
Marco 对。
And if you buy a better TV, then you basically are upgrading or to upgrade.
如果你买一台更好的电视，那基本上就是在升级，或者“to upgrade”。
Katarina Okay, so this verb to upgrade means to go
Katarina 好的，所以动词“to upgrade”意思是
from something that's okay to something that's better.
从还可以的东西变成更好的东西。
Marco Exactly.
Marco 没错。
So in previous lessons, we've seen to get a complimentary upgrade, for example, on a
所以在之前的课程中，我们见过“get a complimentary upgrade”，比如在
flight or in a hotel.
航班或酒店里。
Katarina I like that.
Katarina 我喜欢这个。
Well, you can also get an upgrade on a computer.
嗯，你也可以升级电脑。
You say, well, my computer's from 1994.
你会说：“我的电脑是1994年的。”
I really need to get an upgrade.
“我真的需要升级一下。”
Marco Yeah, for sure.
Marco 是啊，当然。
So to upgrade.
所以“to upgrade”。
Now, we're going to be listening to this dialogue for the first time, we're going to be buying
现在，我们第一次听这段对话，我们要买
a TV.
一台电视。
So let's listen.
所以让我们来听。
Katarina Seriously, I don't know why we need to get
Katarina 说真的，我不明白我们为什么需要买
a new TV.
一台新电视。
Marco Honey, I told you already.
Marco 亲爱的，我已经告诉过你了。
I can't appreciate the graphics level and detail of the games on my PlayStation 3 on
我无法在旧电视上欣赏PlayStation 3游戏的图形水平和细节。
our old TV.
Good afternoon, folks, how can I be of service today?
下午好，两位，今天有什么能帮到你们的？
I'm looking to upgrade to a newer, bigger television set.
我想升级到一台更新、更大的电视机。
You've come to the right place.
你来对地方了。
What size are you looking for?
你想要多大尺寸的？
Just a normal size TV for a living room.
就是客厅用的普通尺寸电视。
I see.
我明白了。
Well, this set here is on sale.
嗯，这台正在打折。
It's a 46 inch HT TV screen and it has all the works three HDMI connectors, USB, VGA
这是一台46英寸的HT电视屏幕，功能齐全，有三个HDMI接口、USB、VGA
and S video ports.
和S视频端口。
It even has a DVI port so you can hook up your PC or laptop.
它甚至还有一个DVI接口，可以连接你的电脑或笔记本。
This is without a doubt the complete home theater experience.
这毫无疑问是完整的家庭影院体验。
This is exactly what I need.
这正是我需要的。
Can you imagine watching movies or playing video games on this thing?
你能想象用这个看电影或玩电子游戏吗？
Katarina Honey, I think it's a bit too big.
Katarina 亲爱的，我觉得有点太大了。
I don't even think it will fit in our living room.
我甚至觉得它放不进我们的客厅。
Not to worry.
别担心。
We will deliver and install it in your home.
我们会送货并安装到你家。
It comes with a wall mount so you can just hang it on the wall like a picture.
它附带一个壁挂支架，所以你可以像挂画一样把它挂在墙上。
This is great.
太棒了。
How much will this set me back?
这个要花我多少钱？
Lucky for you, this is the last one we have in stock, so it's half off.
你运气好，这是库存里的最后一台，所以半价。
I'll take it.
我买了。
All right, so I'm going to have to defer to you, Marco, on some of these words in today's
好的，所以今天语言要点里的有些词，Marco，我得请教你，
language takeaway because they're all about TV specifics.
因为它们都是关于电视的具体术语。
Language takeaway.
语言要点。
All right, the first word that we're going to be looking at is graphics, the graphics
好的，我们要看的第一个词是“graphics”，图形
level.
水平。
All right, so you might have heard this before with the phrase graphic designer, someone
好的，你可能以前听过这个词，比如“graphic designer”，
who designs images.
设计图像的人。
But in this case, we're talking about graphics, so the way things appear on your TV.
但在这里，我们说的是“graphics”，也就是东西在电视上显示的方式。
So basically the pictures, right?
所以基本上就是图像，对吧？
So he wanted to appreciate the graphics of his PlayStation 3 better, and that's why he
所以他想要更好地欣赏PlayStation 3的图形，这就是为什么他
wanted a new TV.
想要一台新电视。
All right, or he could say, my computer has amazing graphics.
好的，或者他可以说：“我的电脑有惊人的图形。”
It means games are really fun because they look good.
意思是游戏因为画面好看而很有趣。
Or this game has amazing graphics, so the game has places or scenery that looks really,
或者“这个游戏有惊人的图形”，所以游戏里的场景看起来非常、
really real.
非常真实。
All right, so graphics.
好的，所以“graphics”。
But some kinds of TVs are made to provide those wonderful graphics, and those are called
但有些类型的电视就是为了提供这些精彩的图形而制造的，它们被称为
HDTV.
HDTV。
Right, and HDTV, or that's an acronym for high definition television.
对，HDTV，那是“high definition television”的缩写。
All right, and I heard some actors and actresses were complaining about HDTV because the picture
好的，我听说有些演员在抱怨HDTV，因为画质
quality is so good that you can see all of the little problems on their face, the little
太好了，你能看到他们脸上所有的小问题，小
wrinkles and the pimples and the scars.
皱纹、痘痘和疤痕。
So be careful because one day we're going to be able to see way too much.
所以要小心，因为有一天我们能看到太多东西了。
Exactly.
没错。
So on high definition television, that's basically what you get is better definition, better level
所以在高清电视上，你得到的基本上就是更好的清晰度，更好的
of graphics.
图形水平。
So more pixels per inch, you can see a lot more clarity.
所以每英寸更多像素，你能看到更清晰的画面。
Right, so an HDTV.
对，所以HDTV。
The next thing we're talking about is actually kind of related to the back part of your TV
接下来我们要说的其实和电视背面
where you plug things in.
插东西的地方有关。
Sometimes it's on the side, sometimes it's on the back.
有时在侧面，有时在背面。
Well, there are different names for different kinds of plugs.
嗯，不同类型的插头有不同的名称。
So today we're going to talk about two of those.
所以今天我们要讲其中两个。
One of them is USB.
一个是USB。
Right, this TV has a USB port, which basically stands for universal serial bus.
对，这台电视有一个USB端口，基本上代表“通用串行总线”。
All right, so a port is a place where you plug something in.
好了，端口就是你插东西的地方。
Your computer has a lot of ports as well.
你的电脑也有很多端口。
But USB is maybe more common for people who have iPods or computers because this is how
但对于有 iPod 或电脑的人来说，USB 可能更常见，因为这是
we normally connect things to our computers.
我们通常连接电脑的方式。
So in this case, this television, you could connect maybe your iPod and reproduce videos
所以在这种情况下，这台电视，你可以连接你的 iPod，然后在电视上播放视频
or pictures onto the TV.
或图片。
Awesome.
太棒了。
Or in the second case, we have a DVI port.
或者第二种情况，我们有一个 DVI 端口。
So DVI, you're going to have to tell me about this one, Marco, because I'm not so sure.
所以 DVI，你得给我讲讲这个，Marco，因为我不太确定。
Well, a DVI is basically a digital video input.
嗯，DVI 基本上是一个数字视频输入接口。
So basically you can connect your computer to the TV and see what's on your screen.
所以基本上你可以把电脑连接到电视上，看到屏幕上的内容。
Nice.
不错。
And so if you have a bunch of movies stored on your computer, you can just plug it into
如果你电脑里存了很多电影，你只需把它插到
the TV and watch.
电视上就能看。
Or you can even navigate the internet on a big screen TV.
或者你甚至可以在大屏幕电视上浏览互联网。
Cool.
酷。
All right.
好的。
So what are these three HDMI connectors?
那这三个 HDMI 接口是干什么的？
All right.
好的。
Well, this is a new technology.
嗯，这是一种新技术。
Basically, you know how before you used to get your DVD player, your VHS, and you had
基本上，你知道以前你用的 DVD 播放器、VHS 录像机，会有
three cables, two for sound and one for video?
三根线，两根音频一根视频吗？
Yeah, the red, yellow, and white cables.
是啊，红、黄、白三根线。
Exactly.
没错。
So with this new type of cable or technology, with one cable, it takes all the information
所以用这种新型线缆或技术，一根线就能把所有信息
to the TV.
传到电视上。
So just one cable for everything.
所以一根线搞定一切。
Oh, nice.
哦，不错。
The problem is I always used to put the wrong cable in the wrong port, so I'd have the red
问题是我以前总是把线插错口，比如把红色
cable in the yellow port, and then I'd say, where's the video?
线插到黄色口上，然后我就说，视频呢？
I can't see.
我看不见。
All I can do is listen.
我只能听。
Yeah, it happens.
是啊，常有的事。
So with this, now it's easy.
所以有了这个，现在就简单了。
And well, it's a little bit more organized, because I remember I used to have a TV and
而且，它也更整齐了，因为我记得我以前有台电视，
I had a lot of different things connected to it.
上面连了好多不同的东西。
It was just this big spider web in the back with all these cables.
后面就像个大蜘蛛网，全是线。
So an HDMI, high definition multimedia interface connector.
所以 HDMI，高清晰度多媒体接口连接器。
And what else do we have?
还有什么？
Well, the last thing we're talking about is actually the place to put your TV.
嗯，我们最后要讲的是放电视的地方。
So a lot of people now are putting their TVs on walls like paintings, because these TVs
现在很多人把电视像画一样挂在墙上，因为这些电视
are so thin.
太薄了。
So we call this a wall mount.
所以我们称之为壁挂支架。
So a mount, to mount something is also a verb, right?
所以 mount，安装某物也是一个动词，对吧？
Yeah, it means to put something up or to hang something up.
是的，意思是把某物放上去或挂起来。
So many people like to mount their trophies to show off.
很多人喜欢把奖杯挂起来炫耀。
Very good.
很好。
So this is what we're doing with the TV.
所以这就是我们对电视的做法。
We're going to mount it on the wall like a painting.
我们要把它像画一样挂在墙上。
Cool.
酷。
So those are our words for language takeaway.
这些就是我们语言学习的词汇。
Let's take another listen to today's dialogue.
让我们再听一遍今天的对话。
We're going to slow it down this time and really figure out what's going on.
这次我们会放慢速度，真正搞清楚发生了什么。
Seriously, I don't know why we need to get a new TV.
说真的，我不明白我们为什么要买新电视。
Honey, I told you already.
亲爱的，我跟你说过了。
I can't appreciate the graphics level and detail of the games on my PlayStation 3 on
我无法在旧电视上欣赏 PlayStation 3 游戏的画质和细节。
our old TV.
Good afternoon, folks.
下午好，各位。
How can I be of service today?
今天有什么能帮到您的？
I'm looking to upgrade to a newer, bigger television set.
我想升级一台更新、更大的电视机。
You've come to the right place.
您来对地方了。
What size are you looking for?
您想要多大尺寸的？
Just a normal sized TV for a living room.
就一个客厅用的普通尺寸电视。
I see.
我明白了。
Well, this set here is on sale.
嗯，这台正在打折。
It's a 46 inch HTTV screen and it has all the works.
这是一台 46 英寸的 HTTV 屏幕，功能齐全。
Three HDMI connectors, USB, VGA, and S-video ports.
三个 HDMI 接口，USB、VGA 和 S-video 端口。
It even has a DVI port so you can hook up your PC or laptop.
它甚至还有一个 DVI 端口，可以连接你的 PC 或笔记本电脑。
This is without a doubt the complete home theater experience.
这毫无疑问是完整的家庭影院体验。
This is exactly what I need.
这正是我需要的。
Can you imagine watching movies or playing video games on this thing?
你能想象用这个看电影或玩游戏吗？
Honey, I think it's a bit too big.
亲爱的，我觉得有点太大了。
I don't even think it will fit in our living room.
我甚至觉得它放不进我们的客厅。
Not to worry.
别担心。
We will deliver and install it in your home.
我们会送货上门并安装。
It comes with a wall mount so you can just hang it on the wall like a picture.
它配有壁挂支架，你可以像挂画一样把它挂在墙上。
This is great.
太好了。
How much will this set me back?
这个要花我多少钱？
Lucky for you, this is the last one we have in stock so it's half off.
算你走运，这是库存最后一台，所以半价。
I'll take it.
我要了。
All right.
好的。
So now we're going to be taking a look at three different phrases that we saw in this
现在我们来看看在 Fluency Builder 部分对话中出现的三个不同短语。
dialogue in Fluency Builder.
Fluency Builder.
Fluency Builder。
All right.
好的。
This first phrase is definitely one that I use a lot.
第一个短语绝对是我经常用的。
We can talk about food.
我们可以谈论食物。
We can talk about electronics.
我们可以谈论电子产品。
We can talk about most different things.
我们可以谈论大多数不同的事情。
But the phrase here is the works.
但这个短语是 the works。
He's getting the works.
他得到了全套配置。
All right.
好的。
That means any option he could get, any possibility, he wants it all.
意思是任何他能得到的选项，任何可能性，他全都要。
Right.
对。
So if you're getting a new car, for example, right, you're getting the high definition
所以如果你买新车，比如，你得到了高清晰度
sound system.
音响系统。
You're getting nice tires, leather seats.
你得到了好轮胎、真皮座椅。
You're getting the works.
你得到了全套配置。
All right.
好的。
Or if you're getting a hamburger and you want the works, you're getting it with cheese and
或者如果你买汉堡，想要全套，你会得到加奶酪、
lettuce and tomato and pepper and bacon and you know, it means every option you're getting
生菜、番茄、辣椒和培根，你知道，意思是每个选项你都要
it all.
全有。
The works.
全套配置。
So I think this word is so versatile that we should maybe listen to some more examples.
所以我觉得这个词非常灵活，我们应该听一些更多的例子。
Example one.
例子一。
The bridegroom was wearing a morning suit, top hat, gloves, the works.
新郎穿着晨礼服、高顶礼帽、手套，全套行头。
Example two.
例子二。
He spent over $10,000 on his home theater system.
他在家庭影院系统上花了超过一万美元。
He got all the works.
他买了全套配置。
Example three.
例子三。
I bought a new car with all the works, magnesium rims, custom paint and leather seats.
我买了一辆新车，带全套配置，镁合金轮毂、定制喷漆和真皮座椅。
So now that we've seen the works on the home theater system, he needs to hook it up.
现在我们看到了家庭影院系统的全套配置，他需要把它连接起来。
All right.
好的。
So this is an important part and a very exciting part of a new purchase.
这是新购买中一个重要且非常令人兴奋的部分。
So when you buy something, you have to hook it up.
所以当你买东西时，你必须把它连接起来。
That means you have to plug things together.
意思是你要把东西插在一起。
Okay.
好的。
So we plug things into the wall for electricity, but also hook up maybe those, those cores
我们把东西插到墙上取电，但也可以连接你之前提到的那些线，
you were talking about earlier, that HDMI connector, that's called hooking up or connecting.
那个 HDMI 连接器，这就叫连接或接上。
So you would hook up your DVD player to your television.
所以你会把 DVD 播放器连接到电视上。
All right.
好的。
I could ask you, did you hook up those new speakers to your big TV yesterday?
我可以问你，你昨天有没有把那些新音箱连接到你的大电视上？
Very good.
非常好。
Right.
对。
So to connect, it's another way of saying to connect.
所以“连接”是另一种表达“连接”的方式。
And finally, the, the big event when you're buying something is the end when you have
最后，当你买东西时，最重要的时刻就是最后你
to actually pay.
必须付钱的时候。
And this guy's a little bit worried that the things he wants cost a lot of money.
这个人有点担心他想要的东西要花很多钱。
So he asks a really great question.
所以他问了一个非常好的问题。
Yeah.
是的。
He said, how much will this set me back?
他说，这个要花我多少钱？
Okay.
好的。
This sounds a little weird at first, because you could just say, how much will this cost?
这听起来一开始有点奇怪，因为你本可以直接说，这个要多少钱？
But he's speaking in a very colloquial way, very familiar.
但他用一种非常口语化、很熟悉的方式在说话。
And he says, how much will this set me back?
他说，这个要花我多少钱？
Right.
对。
So how much will this cost me?
所以这个要花我多少钱？
So how much am I actually going to spend?
所以我实际上要花多少钱？
So it's just a different way of saying how much does it cost?
这只是表达“这个多少钱”的另一种方式。
But it's like you say, more colloquial.
但就像你说的，更口语化。
It's a lot more native-like.
更地道。
Exactly.
没错。
And so if you're writing your paper, you don't want to write this, this will set you back
所以如果你在写论文，你不会想写“这在经济学上会花掉你
$500 in economics.
500美元”。
But we'd say this in spoken language in our normal daily lives with friends.
但我们在日常生活中的口语里，和朋友之间会这么说。
So why don't we listen to a couple more examples of set me back.
那我们再听几个关于“set me back”的例子吧。
Example one.
例子一。
This unexpected expense is going to set us back a couple thousand dollars.
这笔意外的开支会让我们花掉几千美元。
Example two.
例子二。
That fancy dinner at the restaurant last night really set us back.
昨晚那顿高档餐厅的晚餐真的让我们花了不少钱。
Example three.
例子三。
I feel guilty about buying this coat.
买这件外套让我感到内疚。
It set me back over $300.
它花了我超过300美元。
All right.
好的。
Great.
太棒了。
So now that we've taken a look at those great phrases and with some good examples, why don't
现在我们已经看过了那些精彩的短语和一些好例子，不如
we listen to this dialogue one last time.
我们最后再听一遍这段对话。
Seriously, I don't know why we need to get a new TV.
说真的，我不明白我们为什么要买新电视。
Honey, I told you already.
亲爱的，我已经告诉过你了。
I can't appreciate the graphics level and detail of the games on my PlayStation 3 on
我无法在旧电视上欣赏到PlayStation 3游戏的画质和细节。
our old TV.
Good afternoon, folks.
下午好，各位。
How can I be of service today?
今天我能为您服务吗？
I'm looking to upgrade to a newer, bigger television set.
我想升级到一台更新、更大的电视机。
You've come to the right place.
您来对地方了。
What size are you looking for?
您想要多大尺寸的？
Just a normal size TV for a living room.
就是客厅用的普通尺寸电视。
I see.
我明白了。
Well, this set here is on sale.
嗯，这台正在打折。
It's a 46 inch HT TV screen and it has all the works.
这是一台46英寸的HT电视屏幕，功能齐全。
Three HDMI connectors, USB, VGA and S video ports.
三个HDMI接口、USB、VGA和S视频端口。
It even has a DVI port so you can hook up your PC or laptop.
它甚至还有一个DVI端口，这样你就可以连接你的电脑或笔记本电脑。
This is without a doubt, the complete home theater experience.
这毫无疑问是完整的家庭影院体验。
This is exactly what I need.
这正是我需要的。
Can you imagine watching movies or playing video games on this thing?
你能想象用这个看电影或玩电子游戏吗？
Honey, I think it's a bit too big.
亲爱的，我觉得有点太大了。
I don't even think it will fit in our living room.
我甚至觉得它放不进我们的客厅。
Not to worry.
别担心。
We will deliver and install it in your home.
我们会送货上门并安装。
It comes with a wall mount so you can just hang it on the wall like a picture.
它附带一个壁挂支架，所以你可以像挂画一样把它挂在墙上。
This is great.
太棒了。
How much will this set me back?
这个要花我多少钱？
Lucky for you, this is the last one we have in stock so it's half off.
算你走运，这是我们库存的最后一台，所以半价出售。
I'll take it.
我买了。
Okay, so a big TV, I think, I don't know, I think it's just a great thing to have at
好的，所以一台大电视，我觉得，我不知道，我觉得家里有它
home.
是件好事。
Not to, you know, spend too much time in front of the TV but it's good to sit down and watch
不是说要花太多时间在电视前，但坐下来看
a movie.
电影还是不错的。
It's nice because now there's so many different things you can do with it.
很好，因为现在你可以用它做很多不同的事情。
You can hook up your computer, you can buy a projector, you can play your PS3 or your
你可以连接你的电脑，可以买投影仪，可以玩你的PS3或
Wii.
Wii。
So I think there's a lot to do and it's just wonderful how great graphics have come in
所以我觉得有很多事情可以做，而且过去五年里画质的进步
just like the last five years.
真是太棒了。
What do you think about having a television set, for example, in the bathroom?
你觉得在浴室里放一台电视机怎么样？
I would say it's a really bad idea but I think, well, if I have a bathtub, I think it would
我会说这是个很糟糕的主意，但我觉得，嗯，如果我有浴缸，那应该
be really cool.
会很酷。
What about, you know, some people don't like having a television set in their bedroom.
那有些人呢，不喜欢在卧室里放电视机。
I agree with this.
我同意这个观点。
Why?
为什么？
I agree.
我同意。
Because I think it's really important that you have peace and quiet in your bedroom because
因为我觉得在卧室里保持安静很重要，因为
it's kind of like, for me, it's an important space where I can just relax and be quiet
对我来说，这是一个重要的空间，我可以放松、安静下来，
and I like reading a lot so if I have a TV, maybe I'll watch more TV but I'd much rather
而且我很喜欢读书，所以如果有电视，我可能会看更多电视，但我更愿意
read a book before bed.
在睡前读一本书。
True.
没错。
Yeah, I definitely agree but, you know, I've seen people that have TVs in their living
是的，我完全同意，但是，你知道，我见过有人在他们的客厅、
rooms, in their dining rooms, even in their kitchen so they're watching something while
餐厅，甚至厨房里放电视，这样他们做饭的时候也能看点什么，
they're cooking and even in the bathroom.
甚至浴室里也有。
Like you say, in a bathtub, well, it's nice but some of them I've seen in front of the
就像你说的，在浴缸里，嗯，那不错，但我见过一些电视放在
toilet or something.
马桶前面之类的。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
I would say that the one in the kitchen is nice because if you spend a lot of time in
我会说厨房里放一个不错，因为如果你花很多时间在
the kitchen, you can watch the news while you're cooking or you can actually watch
厨房里，你可以边做饭边看新闻，或者实际上可以看
cooking shows and try and practice.
烹饪节目，试着练习一下。
Or soap operas.
或者肥皂剧。
So I guess it depends on the person.
所以我想这取决于个人。
It depends on how much you watch TV.
这取决于你看电视的频率。
But I'm curious to know what our listeners have to say about TVs and big electronics
但我很好奇我们的听众对电视和大型电子产品
purchases.
购买有什么看法。
Right.
对。
So come to our website EnglishPod.com.
所以请访问我们的网站EnglishPod.com。
If you have any questions or any doubts regarding the lesson or any suggestions, you can let
如果你对这节课有任何问题或疑问，或者有任何建议，你可以告诉
us know.
我们。
Otherwise, we'll be there to just talk and practice that English and of course send us
否则，我们会在那里聊天、练习英语，当然也请把你们
your suggestions for future lessons.
对未来课程的建议发给我们。
We love to know what you're interested in learning about.
我们很想知道你们对学习什么感兴趣。
All right.
好的。
We'll see you guys there.
我们到时候见。
All right.
好的。
Take care.
保重。